







Verified : Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 22-Jan-21 Last Modified: 22-Jan-21

Jump to Section Work E

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

Support, Mainframes, Confluence, Cobol, CICS, VSAM, JIRA, ITIL, JCL, DB2

# **Summary**

Overall 5.3 years of total IT experience in Retail Domain.

Having one year of Onsite experience working with Coles Australia in Melbourne at client location handling the onsite team and maintaining offshore-onsite model

Good working knowledge on Manhattan WMS Application (Retail ERP), Manhattan LM, Manhattan TMS with SQL and UNIX as primary skills.

Having good knowledge on retail domain, supply chain and application support apart from WMS.

Handled multiple tasks as part of ITIL life cycle which includes Incident Management, Problem Management, Change

Key Skills: Senior Associate Consultant, Team/Tech Lead, Project Management, Incident Management, Change Management, Defect Management, SQL Development, Requirement Gathering, Agile Methodology, Application

Management and User Management along with the Application testing.

Proactive at defect analysis and defect fixing capabilities

Possess effective communication abilities to deal efficiently with the clients.

To be an astute learner and the consistent performer in your organization. So that I can achieve glorious heights in my career working with a growing company by using my skill sets.

# **Work Experience**

Infosys Limited as WMS Senior Associate Consultant Feb 2020 to Till Date

Project Domain Retail Project Name: Internal Client NA Roles Manhattan WMS Senior Associate Consultant Organization Infosys Ltd. Location Hyderabad Duration February 2020 - Till Date Functional Skills Manhattan WMS Application (Retail ERP), Manhattan LM, Manhattan TMS with SQL and UNIX as primary skills, Incident Management, Problem Management, Change Management Tools SQL Developer, Putty, Control - M, Service Now, HP Life cycle Management, JIRA

Tech Mahindra as Manhattan WMS Consultant-Support Analyst Aug 2015 to Jan 2020

Project Name: Coles Manhattan WMS Client Coles Australia Roles Manhattan WMS Application Support Analyst, Software Engineer, Techno Functional consultant Organization Tech Mahindra Location Hyderabad Duration August 2015 - January 2020 Functional Skills Manhattan WMS Application (Retail ERP), Manhattan LM, Manhattan TMS with SQL and UNIX as primary skills, Incident Management, Problem Management, Change Management Tools SQL Developer, Putty, Control - M. Service Now, HP Life cycle Management, JIRA

Project Overview: Coles is an Australian Supermarket chain which uses warehouse management system (WMS) a software application, designed to support warehouse or distribution center management and staff. They facilitate management in their daily planning, organizing, staffing, directing, and controlling the utilization of available resources, to move and store materials into, within, and out of a warehouse, while supporting staff in the performance of material movement and storage in and around a warehouse.

Responsibilities:

Worked on Manhattan WMS, LM, TMS applications with SQL and UNIX skills. Having a good knowledge on retail industry.

# **Important**

 Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld Mainly supported the project in resolving High critical P1,P2 and normal P3 Issues.

Identifying Blocking issues and resolving them to increase the performance

Main work is to identify functional, procedural and data issues with help of Manhattan UI and Oracle Database Monitoring Unixlogs and job histories for troubleshooting.

Used Tools like SQL Developer, Putty, Service Now, HP Life cycle Management, Control - M, JIRA, Confluence.

Fully Involved in Problem Management (To identify Root cause of repeated issues), Change requests and User requests other than the regular issues.

Strong skills with ability to work under pressure and keep team motivated and focus as we handled high critical P1 issues.

Having good decision making power and readiness to the responsibility. Involved in QC Testing apart from incidents and change requests.

Extensive Experience in handling the tools such as Control-M

Ability to understand and meet the changing business requirements
Compatible team player through complete project cycles, testing and final implementation.

Good at communicating with the clients, and collecting required data from them

Ability to apply good and efficient logic.

Enthusiastic and good communication skills

^ Back to Top

### Education

 $\hbox{UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Bectronics/Telecommunication) from G.Pullaiah College of Engineering, Kurnool in 2015}\\$ 

^ Back to Top

### IT Skills

Skill Name	Version Last Used Experience
Mainframes, Cobol, JCL, VSAM,	
DB2, CICS, SQL, Unix, Oracle	
Putty, Control - M, Service Now,	
Jira, Confluence	

^ Back to Top

# Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English				
Hindi				
Telugu				

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

## **Work Authorization**

Physically Challenged: No

Job Type: Permanent / Temporary Employment Status: Full Time, Part Time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

 ${\it Careers-About\,Us-Clients-Terms\,\&\,Conditions-FAQ's-Contact\,Us-Report\,a\,Problem-Site\,Map-Resources}$ Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.